Was winning worth the cost?
Athlete A is a documentary film directed by Jon Shenk.
Follow the Indianapolis Star reporters that broke the story about USA
Gymnastics doctor Larry Nassar's abuse and hear from gymnasts.
Self - Gymnast, played by Maggie Nichols.
Self, played by Jamie Dantzscher.
Self - Investigations Reporter, The Indianapolis Star, played by Mark Alesia.
Self - Former Gymnast, played by Rachael Denhollander.
Self - Karolyi Choreographer, played by Géza Poszar.
Self - USA Olympic Team 1984, played by Tracee Talavera.
Athlete A is a 2020 American documentary film about
the USA Gymnastics sex abuse scandal.
Directed by Bonni Cohen and Jon Shenk, the documentary follows a team of investigative journalists from The Indianapolis Star as they broke the story of doctor
Larry Nassar sexually assaulting young female gymnasts and the subsequent allegations that engulfed USA Gymnastics (USAG) and its then-CEO Steve Penny.
It was released on June 24, 2020, by Netflix.
The title refers to gymnast Maggie Nichols who was referred to as "Athlete A" to protect her identity
while investigations into her sexual abuse by USAG doctor Larry Nassar were ongoing.
The film explores themes of sexual abuse, sports,
gymnastics, teenage girl, sports documentary.